This is The [IMG:left]
Hellbat Armor. [IMG:left]
This is The [IMG:right]
Hulkbuster Armor. [IMG:right]
So what's the difference? [IMG:wtd]
Most fans think the [IMG:right]
Hulkbuster is the ultimate [IMG:right]
anti-god suit. [IMG:right]
It's [IMG:disagree]
not. [IMG:disagree]
The [IMG:normal]
Hellbat Armor The Hellbat [IMG:left]
suit was forged by [IMG:left]
the Justice League in [IMG:left]
the sun to fight [IMG:left]
Gods, but drains Batman's [IMG:left]
life force. [IMG:left]
But The Hulkbuster Armor [IMG:right]
The Hulkbuster uses heavy [IMG:right]
hydraulic armor plates and [IMG:right]
satellite parts to withstand [IMG:right]
brute physical force. [IMG:right]
The Hulkbuster fights physical [IMG:twohandsopen]
monsters, while the Hellbat [IMG:twohandsopen]
drains life [IMG:remember_this]
to kill Gods. [IMG:remember_this]
Follow for more. [IMG:final_end]